- What on earth are you talking about?
- Let me explain.
(Sheldon:)You see,
I'm a superior genetic mutation...
(Sheldon:)...an improvement
on the existing mediocre stock.
(Missy:)And what do you mean,
"mediocre stock"?
(Sheldon:)That would be you.
(Sheldon:)But residing within you
is the potential for another me.
(Sheldon:)Perhaps even taller, smarter
and less prone to freckling.
(Sheldon:)A Sheldon 2.0, if you will.
- Sheldon 2.0?
- Exactly.
(Sheldon:)Now, I am not saying that I should be
the sole decider of who you mate with.
If you're not attracted, then the likelihood
of conception will be reduced.
- You have got to be kidding me.
- Not at all.
(Sheldon:)Frequent coitus dramatically increases
the odds of fertilization.
(Missy:)Okay, Shelly, sit down.
(Missy:)Now, I've lived my whole life dealing
with the fact that my twin brother is...
(Missy:)...as Mom puts it,
one of God's special little people.